Hi, and that was some I want to do a wind surf code editor over you.
So the wind surf is an ex-generation AI code editor built to keep you in flow.
With wind surf you can code faster and it focuses better.
It will help you code smoothly and easily, it understands your code, gives smart suggestions
and can do hard tasks for you.
It also makes to keep you focused by removing sound distractions and doing boring work,
so we should do normal air.
Potovolque course software has been developed by team of researchers and engineers.
Let's talk now about the main part about the course of features.
So course offers really a big variety of features designed to enhance the coding experience
and productivity.
Let's start with cascade features cascade, it's a chat interface where you can do really
a lot of work.
Cascade is the smartest way to code with AI.
It understands your whole project, gives you helpful tools and watches what they do in real
time to help you work faster and better and it's all in one smooth flow.
So it has full context awareness.
It knows the full context so it works well even on big and live projects.
It suggests and runs some commands, it can find problems suggest commands and runs them
for you to fix or improve your code.
It also can make changes in many files at once and keep everything in sync.
So the next feature is the code top, top, top and cheap, it stops out the complete, so you
can use one top of the top key and give you a really powerful help.
This full feature works only in the Winsort Editor because it's also available in plugins
for different ideas and this plugin supports only some basic out the complete.
So if you want as a full powerness of this feature so you can use Winsort Code Editor.
It has out the complete.
That means you can write your code faster to save time and we're sorry we'll suggest
you some code.
It has also super complete feature, it gets us what you want to do next, not just the
line, the next line, but just the next place in the file.
You can click top to jump, it moves you to the source where you will likely edit next,
it tries to predict and it also can automatically add some imports to a file so you shouldn't
care about it.
The next feature is command, it's inline shot interface which allows you to generate some
new code or existing code directly in the digital window from a specific place.
It can transform your ideas and the code with some natural language prompts and of course
you can select some code and ask some quick questions like request some improvement
to fix the bug at the bug end so let's not talk about availability, so the Winsort
available for all platforms for all desktop platforms like Mark, Windows and Linux.
And it has some plugins for the most popular code leaders, like VS Code, JetBrains, Visual Studio,
NEL, VIM, Xcode, it also supports VIM and Eclipse and might be some others so you can always
check the actual list on the website.
Okay, I hope this quick overview was useful for you and now we know what is console
what feature it has and see you in the next lesson.